KEVIN TRAN

1365 Linden ave, Glendale, CA | (818) 913-3157 | kevin_tran95@yahoo.com

OBJECTIVE

Detail-Oriented Psychology Major (3.0 GPA) graduated from California State University-Northridge, with 5.5 years of work experience. My goal is to be the best web developer that I can be and contribute as much as I can to the technology industry. I am dedicated to perfecting my craft by learning from more seasoned developers and continuously make strides to learn all that I can.

EXPERIENCE

Crisis Counselor

Crisis Text Line | May 2021 - Present

- Assessed risk to clients through established evaluation procedures
- Utilized motivational interviewing in helping individuals for a cohesive plan to achieve short and long term goals
- Effectively collaborated with service providers and advocate on behalf of consumer

Behavior Interventionist

Intercare Therapy, Inc | Mar 2021 – Jul 2021

- Provided services in home, school, and community to children with autism and other developmental disabilities.
- Trained and counseled parents on how to handle inappropriate behaviors to help their children
- Helped reduce the frequency, duration, and intensity of maladaptive behaviors while increasing the probability of appropriate behaviors.

Waiter

Glendale Pho Co | Sept 2013 - Feb 2020

- Successfully communicate with customers and respond appropriately to positive and negative feedback. (ie, via Yelp review and in-person)
- Manage eMarketing vendors and platforms (ex: Yelp, Postmates, Ubereats, etc.)
- Assisted the manager with training new employees, ensuring they possessed a full understanding of restaurant policies.

EDUCATION

California State University, Northridge

GPA: 3.0

Northridge, CA

Bachelor of Arts, Major in Psychology (Expected graduation Jun 2021) Dean's List (Fall 2020)

Pasadena City College

Pasadena, CA

Associate in Arts-Natural Science, Social and Behavioral Science, Psychology (Jun 2018)

SPECIAL SKILLS

- Programming languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, and Handlebars
- Microsoft office: Excel, Word, PowerPoint